http://www.leg.state.fl.us/cgi-bin/View_Page.pl?File=privacy.html&Directory=welcome/&Location=app&Tab=info_center&Submenu=4

December 11, 2020
Search Statutes:
Citator
Statutes, Constitution,
Joint Legislative Committees & Other Entities
Joint Administrative Procedures Committee (JAPC)
Joint Committee on Public Counsel Oversight(JCPO)
Joint Legislative Auditing Committee (JLAC)
Joint Legislative Budget Commission (JLBC)
Joint Select Committee on Collective Bargaining (JSCB)
Office of Program Policy Analysis & Government Accountability (OPPAGA)
Auditor General
Commission on Ethics
Economic and Demographic Research (EDR)
Florida Historic Capitol
Historical Committees
Florida Legislative Committee on Intergovernmental Relations (LCIR)
Joint Legislative Committee on Everglades Oversight (JCEO)
Joint Legislative Sunset Committee (JCSC)
Privacy Statement
Thank you for visiting the Florida Legislature's website, Online Sunshine. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit Online Sunshine, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us.
Browsing and Downloading Information
When you visit Online Sunshine, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information. This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service, which uses cookies to collect anonymous traffic data.
In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved. This information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected, and your personal information is not identified.
Sending E-Mail or Providing Other Information
If you choose to share personal information, such as by subscribing to an e-newsletter, sending a message, or filling out an electronic form, please be aware that under Florida law, e-mail addresses are public records. If you do not want your e-mail address released in response to a public-records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact this office by phone or in writing.
Some of the information you provide may be saved for a designated period of time in order to comply with the state of Florida's record retention policies.
If you have questions about Online Sunshine privacy policies, or have suggestions on how these policies can be improved, please feel free to call the Division of Law Revision and Information Services at (850) 488-4371.
Send correspondence to the Division of Law Revision and Information Services, Room 612 Claude Pepper Building, 111 West Madison Street, Tallahassee, FL 32399-1400.
Copyright © 1995-2020 The Florida Legislature • Privacy Statement • Contact Us
